let questionArr = [
  {
    question: "HTML - what is true for a block level element?",
    correctAnswer: "<section> is a block level element",
    wrongAnswer1: "only take up as much space as necessary",
    wrongAnswer2: "both answers above are true"
  },
  {
    question: "HTML - Which of the following are empty tags, meaning no closing tag is needed?",
    correctAnswer: "<br> tag",
    wrongAnswer1: "<a> tag",
    wrongAnswer2: "both tags are empty tags"
  },
  {
    question: "CSS - Choose the correct selector specificity in a descending order?",
    correctAnswer: "Inline > ID > Class > Type",
    wrongAnswer1: "Inline > Class > ID > Type",
    wrongAnswer2: "ID > Class > Inline > Type"
  },
  {
    question: "CSS - given the following properties. Choose the only valid option to CSS …",
    correctAnswer: "text-color: white;",
    wrongAnswer1: "direction-flex: row;",
    wrongAnswer2: "align-self: center"
  },
  {
    question: "What are the names of our Bootcamp Web Dev dogs?",
    correctAnswer: "Tom and Jerry",
    wrongAnswer1: "Touve and Emma",
    wrongAnswer2: "Alfa and Dalula"
  },
  {
    question: "Event Loop",
    correctAnswer: "O1",
    wrongAnswer1: "O2",
    wrongAnswer2: "O3"
  },
  {
    question: "JS - For interpolation of a variable in a string, we use …",
    correctAnswer: "backticks",
    wrongAnswer1: "square bracket",
    wrongAnswer2: "single quates "
  },
  {
    question: "JS - What is true about the .includes () method?",
    correctAnswer: "it is not case sensitive ",
    wrongAnswer1: "returns a boolean ",
    wrongAnswer2: "does not work on strings "
  },
  {
    question: "JS - The return number of .localeCompare method is …",
    correctAnswer: "-1 if reference string is after compared string ",
    wrongAnswer1: "1 if reference string is before compared string",
    wrongAnswer2: "depends on the length of the string"
  },
  {
    question: "JS - Statements with logical operators",
    correctAnswer: "!(4 > 2) 	// => true",
    wrongAnswer1: "false && (anything) is a short-circuit evaluated to true",
    wrongAnswer2: "true  || false      // => true"
  },
  {
    question: "JS - what is the difference between .slice() and .substring()",
    correctAnswer: "there is no difference ",
    wrongAnswer1: ".slice() also supports a negative number",
    wrongAnswer2: ".substring() also supports a negative number"
  },
  {
    question: "JS - Boolean, undefined, symbol and null. Which of this primitives and immuntable?",
    correctAnswer: "they all are primitives and immutable",
    wrongAnswer1: "boolean and null",
    wrongAnswer2: "undefined and null"
  }
];